In this segment of how to lose your slice and get a hook I'm going to relate hooking to hitting a tennis forehand with top spin.
Oh, I know what you're thinking.
"I gave up tennis when I found out making love meant not scoring!"
Bob Hope, 1942.
But, if you could hit top spin and that ball is going to hook in tennis.
The same movements can get you to hook the ball in golf.
So, if you take a golf club and you could actually practice with one hand, tee up a ball with a 7 iron, let's say, and nice and easy make believe you have a tennis racket.
And you're going to hit a top spin forehand.
Racket back, you're hand and arm go out to the right and you're turning it over.
You see that that's the move that has got me to win four US Opens in tennis.
What a great story, can't go into it right now.
We only have two minutes.
Right there.
Forehand with top spin.
Tennis players, you know what I'm talking about.
Now, if you want to do it with two hands make believe it's a two hand forehand with top spin.
You can see that that's going to hook the ball.
Then when you're on the golf course, don't go, "Oh, I'm going to keep my head down."
Think about that during your swing. Tennis. Racket back. Top spin. And, you too, could be like me, winning US Opens in golf and in tennis.
I don't know if they'll believe that one.